zimengine.com 2007-12-11

# LandlordPortal.com™: When success is necessary!

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |   
|   
|  |  |   
|   
|    
|  Logged-off ( login here )  | 

 Tuesday, December 11, 2007  
  
---|---  
   
|  | 

**Welcome !!**  
  
---  

Forms & Agreements  
Tenant Screening  
News Headlines  
Post Rentals FREE!  
Discussion Forums  
FREE Software  
Landlord Certification  
Landlord eBook Guide  
Laws & Legal Guides  

**Member Login**  
  
| Login |   
---|---  
Pass: |   
  
No Account? Signup here..  

| 

**myLocal State Portal™**  
  
---  
  
**California**  
  
|   
---  
**State Directory**  
California State Government State Directory  
**Statewide Offices**  
Attorney General  
California On-Line Directory Statewide Offices  
Governor  
Insurance Commissioner  
Lt. Governor  
Secretary of State  
State Auditor  
State Board of Equalization  
State Controller  
State Treasurer  
**Boards and Commissions**  
Board of Behavioral Sciences  
Board of Prison Terms  
Board of Vocational Nursing and Psychiatric Techni  
Building Standards Commission  
California Arts Council  
California Horse Racing Board  
California Postsecondary Education Commission  
California Transportation Commission  
California Victim Compensation and Government Clai  
Commission on Peace Officer Standards and Training  
Commission on State Mandates  
Commission on Teacher Credentialing  
Commission on the Status of Women  
Delta Protection Commission  
Fair Political Practices Commission  
Little Hoover Commission  
Managed Risk Medical Insurance Board  
Medical Board of California  
Office of Real Estate Appraisers  
Public Utilities Commission  
Seismic Safety Commission  
State Board of Education  
Student Aid Commission  
Youth and Adult Correctional Agency Board of Corre  
**Legislative Branch**  
Legislative Analyst's Office  
Legislative Counsel of California  
Official California Legislative Information  
State Assembly  
State Senate  
Superintendent of Public Instruction Legislative B  
**Judicial Branch**  
California Law Revision Commission Judicial Branch  
**Executive Branch**  
Business, Transportation and Housing Agency Califo  
California Lottery  
California National Guard  
California Public Employees' Retirement System  
California Technology, Trade and Commerce Agency.   
Department of Finance  
Department of Food and Agriculture  
Department of Industrial Relations  
Department of Personnel Administration  
Environmental Protection Agency CalGOLD: Business   
Governor's Office of Emergency Services  
Governor's Office on Service and Volunteerism  
Health and Human Services Agency CalJOBS Departmen  
Judicial Branch Executive Branch  
Office of Administrative Law  
Office of the Inspector General  
Office of the State Public Defender  
Resources Agency California Coastal Commission Cal  
State and Consumer Services Agency Board of Archit  
State Library  
**Regional**  
Association of Bay Area Governments  
Butte County Association of Governments  
Council of Fresno County Governments  
Kern Council of Governments  
Merced County Association of Governments  
Metropolitan Transportation Commission  
Sacramento Area Council of Governments  
San Diego Association of Governments (SANDAG)  
San Luis Obispo Council of Governments  
San Luis Obispo Local Agency Formation Commission  
Santa Clara County Cities Association  
Southern California Association of Governments  
Veterinary Medical Board Regional  
**Libraries**  
Local Government Commission Libraries  
**Other**  
California Association of County Treasurers and Ta  
California Association of Public Purchasing Office  
California Communities  
California Municipal Revenue and Tax Association  
California Society of Municipal Finance Officers  
California Special Districts Association  
California State Association of Counties  
CPS Human Resource Services  
League of California Cities  
Woodside Other  

| Privacy Statement  
---  
  
### Privacy Policy

LandlordPortal respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use LandlordPortal's website and services ("LandlordPortal Site Services"). Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). 

### LandlordPortal and Cookies 

Upon your first visit to LandlordPortal, LandlordPortal sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. LandlordPortal uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. LandlordPortal does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people search. LandlordPortal will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the LandlordPortal Website Service may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

### What Information Do We Collect? 

LandlordPortal does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. LandlordPortal notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. For example, LandlordPortal may use your IP address or browser language to determine which language to use when showing search results or advertisements.

### Links to Other Sites 

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by LandlordPortal Site Services are developed by people over whom LandlordPortal exercises no control. Other links, such as those for the LandlordPortal-friends mailing list archive, are also on sites not controlled by LandlordPortal. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. LandlordPortal may choose to exhibit its search results in the form of a "URL redirecter." When LandlordPortal uses a URL redirecter, if you click on a URL from a search result, information about the click is sent to LandlordPortal, and LandlordPortal in turn sends you to the site you clicked on. LandlordPortal uses this URL information to understand and improve the quality of LandlordPortal's search technology. For instance, LandlordPortal uses this information to determine how often users are satisfied with the first result of a query and how often they proceed to later results. 

### With Whom Does LandlordPortal Share Information? 

LandlordPortal may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average LandlordPortal user visits LandlordPortal, or which other query words are most often used with the query word "Linux." Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

### Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy 

By using the LandlordPortal Site Services and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. LandlordPortal may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

### Who can I ask if I have additional questions? 

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. Our email address is support@LandlordPortal.com.   

|   
  |    

Our Privacy Statement. Our Service Agreement. © 1997 - 2005 LandlordPortal.com, PropertyThree Technology Group All Rights Reserved.

|    
  
* * *

|    

|    
  |    
|    
  
Landlording & Laws

Tenant Screening

Forms & Agreements

Discussions

Rentals & Software

Membership

News Headlines

Landlord Associations

Apartment Associations

Finding & Screening Tenants

Leases Agreements & Move-in

Tenant & Landlord Liabilities

Collections & Rent Control

Repair & Maintenance Duties

Eviction & Lease Termination

Real Estate Open Directory (REOD.org)

Bookstore

Reference & Tools

Landlord Certification

List Rentals

Do-It-Yourself

HUD Popular Links

HUD Housing

Legal Guides

Landlording eGuide Book

Home

Advertising to find tenants

Credit History & References

Anti-discrimination Laws

Avoiding Discrimination

Leases vs Rental Agreements

Lease & Agreement Templates

Clean Up & Preparing to Rent

Moving in a New Tenant

Inspections & Checklists

General Rules of Entry

Landlord Liability for Injuries

Liability & Property Insurance

Asbestos Health Hazards

Lead Health Hazards

Radon Health Hazards

Carbon Monoxide Health Hazards

Establishing Rent Due Dates

Early Payment Incentives

Raising the Rent

Rent Control & Monitoring

Implied Warranty of Habitability 

Meeting Your Legal Responsibilities 

Tenant Responses To Unfit Property 

Tenant Repairs & Maintenance 

Maintenance & Repair System 

Tenant Alterations & Improvements

Terminating Notices

Ways Leases End 

Breaking Leasees 

Lease or Rental Violoations 

Legal Responsibilities Violations 

Illegal Activities on the Premises 

Illegal Evictions

Avoiding Charges of Retaliations

Accounting & Taxation

Appraisers

Associations

Commercial

Computer Software

Construction 

Credit & Screening

Directories & Portals

Employment

Home Builders

Home Buying

Insurance

Investment

Landlord Tenant

Landscaping

Legal

Mortgage & Finance

Moving & Storage

News & Publications

Rentals & Apartments

Senior Living

Services & Vendors

Shopping

Training

Civil Nuisance Laws

Consumer Protection Offices 

Defective Housing 

Federal Housing Laws 

Forms & Agreements 

Landlord Entry Laws 

Landlord Retaliation Laws 

Landlord State Laws 

Lead Paint Hazards 

Lease Termination by State 

Routine Maintenance 

State Appraisal Boards 

State Fair Housing Agencies 

Security Deposit Deadlines 

LandlordPortal Bookstore

Landlord Related Books

Tenant Related Books

General Real Estate Books

California

Florida

Massachusetts

North Carolina

New York

Pennsylvania

Texas

Washington

Calculators

Spanish Translation

View your Education & Testing Progress

Take Exam Number 1

Take Exam Number 2

Take Exam Number 3

Take Exam Number 4

Take Exam Number 5

Take Exam Number 6

Take Exam Number 7

Take Exam Number 8

Take Exam Number 9

Take Exam Number 10

Take Exam Number 11

Take Exam Number 12

List New Rental FREE

Manage Listed Rentals

Search for Rentals at VacancyNet.com

Visit VacancyNet.com

Appliances

Cleaning Supplies

Doors and Windows

Driveways & Paths

Electricals & Lights

Flooring

Garden Center

Gutters

Insulation

Kitchen and Bathroom

Mold & Mildew

Paint

Plumbing

Safety and Security

Stairs

Storage

Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) reading room

Public, assisted, and Native American housing

Homeless

Cities/communities

Community links

Fair housing

Lead hazard

Funding

Legal information

Congressional activity

Labor relations

Web Management

HUD management and other info

Federal sources

HUD Archives

Professional organizations

Good Stories collection

General Housing Info

Single Family Housing

Design technology publications

Fair housing/fair lending publications

Housing finance publications

Housing for special needs publications

Manufactured housing publications

Market characteristics publications 

Affordable housing publications 

Minimum property standards 

About housing 

Housing counseling clearinghouse 

Electronic data interchange access guide 

HUD mortgagee letters 

HUD/FHA housing reports 

More housing information 

Looking for the best mortgage: shop, compare, negotiate 

FHA approved condos 

FHA approved Planned Unit Developments (PUDs) 

Loss mitigation 

FHA connection 

Single family mortgage insurance premiums 

Selling HUD owned homes for HUD 

Real estate settlement procedures act 

Settlement information 

Interstate land sales 

Manufactured housing consumer guide 

Manufactured housing & construction standards 

Technical suitability of products 

Officer next door 

Housing rehab 

More for lenders 

More for real estate brokers 

Landlord Tenant Laws by State

Disclosure Form for Lead Paid and Related Hazards

Real Estate Appraisal Board by State

Lease Termination Notice by State

English Spanish Real Estate Translation

Landlord Deadlines to Itemize and Return Security Deposit

Housing Laws

Fair Housing Agencies by State

The Five Environmental Hazards and Resource

Consumer Protection Offices by State

Violation & Lease Termination Laws by State

Lead-Based Paint Regulations By State

Landlords Entry Laws by State Laws

Options for Tenants with Defective Housing

Landlord Prohibiting Retaliation State Laws

Common Misconceptions about Routine Maintenance

Civil and Criminal Nuisance Laws

Sec. 3604. Discrimination in the Sale or Rental of Housing

Civil Nuisance Laws

Consumer Protection Offices 

Defective Housing 

Federal Housing Laws 

Forms & Agreements 

Landlord Entry Laws 

Landlord Retaliation Laws 

Landlord State Laws 

Lead Paint Hazards 

Lease Termination by State 

Routine Maintenance 

State Appraisal Boards 

State Fair Housing Agencies 

Security Deposit Deadlines 

Tenant Screening Overview and Pricing

Basic Experian Credit Report no Score

CriminalScope™ National Criminal Records Search

Detailed Experian Credit Report w/FICO Score

PatriotVerify™ Global Terrorist Search

SexOffenderWatch™ National SexOffender Search

VerifyBundle™ Basic Package

VerifyBundle™ Deluxe Package

VerifyPlus™ Applicant Background Check

FREE Screening-only Membership Signup

Premium Members Screening Console Login

Thousands of Forms & Agreements 

Maintenance/Management Forms 

Rentals & Leases

Collection/Violation Notices 

Evictions 

Application/Verification Forms 

Contracts 

Signatures and Notary Acknowledgements 

Powers of Attorney 

Assignments

Releases 

Business Operation Agreements 

Miscellaneous Documents 

Promissory Notes 

Sale of Goods 

Financing Documents 

Sale of Personal Property

Discussions & Interaction

General Forum

Landlord Tenant Law Forum

DeadBeat & Skip Warning Forum

Investing Forum

Forms & Agreements Forum

Income Property Forum

Legal & Court Forum

Financing & Mortgage Forum

Maintenance & Repair Forum

Download FREE PropertyThree Software FREE

Visit the PropertyThree Home Page

Post New Rental Listing

Manage All Posted Rentals

Search for Rental Listings

visit VacancyNet.com

myLandlordPortal Profile

Signup

Screening-only Membership Signup

Login

Support

Event Reminder
